Welcome to Saturday Enrichment here at Bodwell
보드웰의 토요 심화 학습 시간에 오신 것을 환영합니다
Also known as "E-Block" or "Saturday E".
‘E-Block’ 또는 ‘Saturday E’라고도 불리죠
This is an opportunity for students to wake up
이 시간 동안 학생은 학기 중 10번
on Saturday mornings 10 times in a term.
토요일 아침에 일어나서
have classes for 3 hours with instructors from the community or here at the school
학교 선생님 및 외부 강사에게 다양한 주제 및 기술 분야에 관해
in a wide variety of topics and skill areas.
3시간 동안 수업을 듣게 됩니다.
Why do we do Saturday E?
그럼 심화 학습은 왜 하는 것일까요?
We do it for a number of reasons, one of the reasons is
여러 가지 이유가 있는데 그 중 하나는
it helps students to improve their English
학생의 영어를 향상하도록
and it gives them more time to practice and use English in different contexts
다양한 내용을 구사하며 더 연습시키는데 있습니다
Other reasons include: we want students to
다른 이유로는 학생이
spend more time to explore different passions,
다양한 열정, 직업 체험, 기술
career options, different skills
그리고 삶에서 중요한 다른 분야를
and different areas of pursuits in life.
더 탐구해보도록 하는데 있습니다
It helps them stand out on their university applications with a lot more experience
이를 통해 대학 원서를 낼 때 더욱 주목받을 수 있고
It helps them have connections to the community
견학, 초청 강연 등을 통해
through doing field trips and meeting different interesting guest speakers,
실세계와의 커넥션이 형성될 수 있습니다
It helps them get real world knowledge about different careers
또한 학생은 다양한 직업에 대한 실전 지식과
different interesting things that are happening in the world
세상의 흥미로운 시사에 대해 배울 수 있습니다
and finally, it allows students to make good use of their weekend time
마지막으로 학생은 특별한 환경 속 실전 학습을 위해
for real learning in a unique setting.
주말의 시간을 잘 활용할 수 있습니다
Each term the students have the opportunity to choose
매 학기 학생은 영어 실력 및 학년에 따라
from a wide variety of classes depending on their English and grade level.
다양한 종류의 수업을 들을 수 있는 기회를 갖습니다
for students in the younger grades and beginner level English,
주니어 또는 영어 실력이 부족한 학생은
we have opportunities for them is classes such as
생활 영어, 여행 및 관광, 기술과 문화 등의
English For Life,  Travel and Tourism, Crafts and Cultures
수업을 들어볼 수 있습니다
We blend English learning with other topics and interesting content
수업은 영어를 다른 주제 및 흥미로운 컨텐츠와 결합시킵니다
For students in the senior grades and with stronger English
시니어 또는 영어 실력이 뛰어난 학생은
we have much more challenging courses in the areas of
스포츠와 그 이상, 공학, 컴퓨터 과학, 일렉트로닉 음악,
Sports and Beyond, Engineering, Computer Science, and Electronic Music IESTS test prep.
IELTS 준비반 등 더욱 심화된 수업을 들어볼 수 있습니다
English 12 support and many, many other courses
그 밖에 English 12 지원 및 기타 많은 코스들이 준비되어 있습니다
Students often find that we  add new and innovative courses each term
매 학기마다 새롭고 혁신적인 수업이 개발되어
And we try to have a wide variety of themes
경영, 체육, 야외 활동, 시민사회, 봉사, 직업 등
from business to outdoors, athletics, citizenship, volunteering, careers and many other areas as well
다양한 주제를 다루고 있는 것을 보실 수 있습니다
From what I 've experienced students don't mind coming into school Saturday morning
제가 본 바로는 학생들이 토요일 오전에 수업 듣는 것을 싫어하지 않습니다
they actually enjoy the opportunity to get to know people with similar interests
학생들은 비슷한 관심사의 사람들을 알아가고
who share their interests
관심사를 공유하는 것을 좋아합니다
and they have the opportunity to explore those interests together
심화 학습 시간에는 그 취미를 같이 탐구해 볼 수 있습니다
They really love the opportunity to meet mentors and professionals in their fields of interest
또한 관심분야 속 멘토와 전문가들을 만날 수 있어서
and they have a lot of fun in the process
그 과정을 통해 많은 재미를 느낍니다
The benefits are very clear.
혜택은 매우 뚜렷합니다
Students will gain more confidence, more passion, curiosity
심화 학습을 통해 학생은 자신감, 열정, 호기심을 얻고
and more well-roundedness.through this program
더욱 균형잡힌 학생이 될 수 있습니다
I expect students to put in a lot of time and commitment and energy
저는 학생들이 많은 열정과 에너지를 쏟길 바라고
In the end the will receive a lot of benefit through this unique opportunity here at Bodwell.
나중에 이 값진 기회를 통해 큰 혜택을 받을 것이라 생각합니다